

DISHANT NILESH JOSHI

Nationality: Indian (+91) 9924451948

Date of birth: 14 Aug 1995

Gender: Male

Email address: joshidishant61.dj@gmail.com

• Address: 6,ANAND DUPLEX APPARTMENT BHAIKAKANAGAR,THALTEJ, 380058

AHMEDABAD (India)

ABOUT ME

CAREER OBJECTIVE To work for a reputed organization, and reveal my all-embracing skills in Customer Service, and Management Work. PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY An ambitious professional with the experience of 4+ years in operations activities with effective communication skills and excellent presentation & soft skills with honed marketing management, logical and problem-solving abilities. Recognized for successfully meeting the targets, high-performing team member and nurturing relationships with clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IMMIGRATION MANAGER

AGILE CONSULTANCY [26 Dec 2020 - 31 Jan 2021]

City: AHMEDABAD Country: India

 Monitor efficient working of Canada/Australia immigration programs and assist to provide appropriate response to all immigration questions and resolve all issues according to required legal requirements.

- Maintain and update log for all VISA and maintain knowledge on all status and assist to hire and terminate all employees and supervise all internal processes and manage all visa petitions.
- Coordinate with All running clients to provide status for same and manage all Immigration files and prepare all visa documents and maintain record for all allowances.
- Maintain knowledge on Canada & Australia Immigration Categories and provide changes to same as per requirements and coordinate with various teams to maintain all immigration applications and

collaborate with human resource and legal teams to resolve all immigration issues for Canada &

Australia.

- Collaborate with staff and boarding teams to recommend appropriate requirements for all visa work within required timeframe and administer delivery of all legal services to all individuals and firms.
- Provide an interface for all immigration processes for global mobility team and maintain knowledge of all immigration requirements and coordinate with external firms to design all processes and

maintain track of all work visa status and prepare reports for human resources.

 $^\circ$ Responsible to Appoint Necessary back office executive , staff person for qualtity, Noc and After submission (job search guidance) process, reporting, training, Motivation. Also give incentives for New

Enrollments.

 Assist all Junior Staff with all permanent residency case information as per requirements and prepare documents for same and design and prepare report metrics for al immigration processes and

programs.

VISA PROCESS EXECUTIVE

AGILE CONSULTANCY [2 Jun 2020 – 25 Dec 2020]

City: AHMEDABAD Country: India

- Counseling is Given to Client Regarding whole Procedure for Student visa, visitor visa, investor visa & Canada immigration.
- Addressed client queries and provided prompt solution through email and telephone.
- My Responsibilities in this role Included Form Filling of Visitor Visa & Business Visa of Canada.
- $\circ\,$ Secondly Document Arrangement Done For Pr File For Express Entry, nova Scotia, Saskatchewan &Etc
- Solving query of Client regarding process ongoing File by Telephonic & Explaining in brief.

BACK OFFICE EXECUTIVE

RAO CONSULTANT PRIVATE LIMITED [21 Oct 2019 - 21 May 2020]

City: AHMEDABAD
Country: India

- My Responsibilities in this role Included Form Filling of Visitor Visa & Business Visa of Canada.
- Secondly I was doing Document Arrangement For Pr File For Express Entry, nova Scotia, Saskatchewan & Etc. .
- Also I Dealing with Client on Absent of Advisor, Counseling is Given to Client Regarding whole Procedure of Canada immigration.
- Solving query of Client regarding process ongoing File by Telephonic & Explaining in brief.

BACK OFFICE EXECUTIVE

WINNY IMMIGRATION AND EDUCATION SERVICE PVT LTD [19 Apr 2019 - 19 Oct 2019]

City: AHMEDABAD
Country: India

- In this role Included Form Filling of Visitor Visa & Business Visa of Canada. Secondly Document Arrangement Done For Pr File For Express Entry, nova Scotia & Saskatchewan Etc.
 - Also I Checking that Client is Eligible for Express Entry & All province .
- ° Also I Dealing with Client on Absent of Advisor, Counseling is Given to Client Regarding whole Procedure of Canada immigration.
 - Solving query of Client regarding process on going File by Telephonic & Explaining in brief.

Operations Officer

VFS GLOBAL PRIVATE LIMITED [27 Aug 2018 – 18 Apr 2019]

City: AHMEDABAD
Country: India

- Basically it is a customer service visa facilitation services, so I have deal with applicant daily 60-80.
- I was taking applications and checking all the documents as per consulate checklist.
- than after I have to verify the application form and after that bio-metric is been taken of applicant than after I

have to do so mean it data entry of the applicant and generating the receipt & In the last I was doing audit of all the documents.

Customer representative

COLES EXPRESS [15 Oct 2015 - 24 Apr 2016]

City: MELBOURNE **Country:** Australia

- I had worked in Coles Express store which is having the Fuel and Convenience retailers store
- I have to fill up the whole the store.
- I have to check the product is expired or not. .
- I have to face up the store.
- To serve the customer and advance customer skills with good presentable behavior.
- Prepared bill/receipts and collected payment from customers.

MARKETING CONTRACTOR

TELSTRA PVT LTD [1 Apr 2015 - 1 Oct 2015]

City: MELBOURNE Country: Australia

- Expand market penetration by building Effective Customer Relations.
- Create & execute appropriate Marketing plan in order to solicit Business.
- Perform Presentations and Demonstrations of Products.
- Meet personal sales goals by Employing workable strategies.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

NEW LJ COMMERCE COLLEGE [6 Oct 2016 – 15 May 2018]

Address: LJ Institute of Media & Communications, Makarba, 382210 AHMEDABAD (India)

CERTIFICATE IV IN BUSINESS

ALTEC COLLEGE [6 Apr 2015 - 4 Oct 2015]

Address: Level 5/601 Bourke St, Melbourne, 3000 MELBOURNE (Australia)

DIMPLOMA IN BUSINESS

ALTEC COLLEGE [5 Oct 2015 - 3 Apr 2016]

Address: Level 5/601 Bourke St, Melbourne, 3000 MELBOURNE (Australia)

MASTER OF COMMERCE

GUJARAT UNIVERSITY [2 Jun 2019 – Current]

Address: Administrative Office(Tower), Navarangpura, 380009 AHMEDABAD (India)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Gujarati

Other language(s):

English Hindi

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1 LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Microsoft Word Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft Excel Microsoft Outlook / SOCIAL MEDIA / The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Exploring new things | Listening music | Traveling

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL & PERSONAL SKILLS

- Analytical Skills
- Problem Solving Skills
- Teamwork
- Adaptability
- Quick learner
- Self-motivated
- Self-disciplined
- Ability to work under pressure.